Guide to the Beryl Graves collection of Laura (Riding) Jackson correspondence, 1925-1940.
Beryl Graves collection of Laura (Riding) Jackson correspondence, 1925-1940.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Beryl Graves collection of Laura (Riding) Jackson correspondence, 1925-1940.
6301
Beryl Graves
.2 cubic ft.
Personal records and correspondence.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Consists of personal records and correspondence pertaining to Laura (Riding) Jackson, collected by Beryl Graves. The correspondence includes letters exchanged between Laura (Riding) Jackson and a variety of corespondents, including Schuyler B. Jackson, publishers Arthur Barker and Constable, and Nancy Cunard. There are also several letters to Robert Graves.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Beryl Graves (Hodge) is the wife of English poet and author Robert Graves. Their relationship started in 1940 and continued until his death.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Consists of personal records and correspondence pertaining to Laura (Riding) Jackson, collected by Beryl Graves. The correspondence includes letters exchanged between Laura (Riding) Jackson and a variety of corespondents, including Schuyler B. Jackson, publishers Arthur Barker and Constable, and Nancy Cunard. There are also several letters to Robert Graves.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Graves, Beryl,; Cunard, Nancy, 1896-1965.; Graves, Robert, 1895-; Jackson, Laura (Riding), 1901-; Jackson, Schuyler B.
Subjects:
American literature--20th century.; American literature--20th century.; Authors, American.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Correspondence: incoming
  - [Author unknown, incomplete letter], July 2, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Barker, Arthur, Jan. 23-Feb. 3, 1933 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Constable & Co., Feb. 3-Mar. 7, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Coyle, Cathleen, July 20-Aug. 1, 1933 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Correspondence: outgoing
  - Dec. 31, 1931-Mar. 11, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Aug. 8, 1939-July 24, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Divorce judgment between Laura Gottschalk and Louis Gottschalk, issued by the Jefferson County (KY) Circuit Court, 1925 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Passport issued to Laura R. Gottschalk, 1925 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Cedula personal, certificate issued to Laura Riding in Deya, Majorca, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 4)